 const  questions = [
  {
    id:1,
    question:'What do you love most in life?',
    answers:[{answer:"GLORY",marks:30},{answer:"KNOWLEDGE",marks:20},{answer:"FAME",marks:0}
    ,{answer:'POWER',marks:40},{answer:'FRIENDSHIP',marks:10}]
  },
  {
    id:2,
    question:'How would your friends describe you?',
    answers:[{answer:"PRETTY",marks:0},{answer:"SMART",marks:20},{answer:"LOYAL",marks:10}
      ,{answer:'PROUD',marks:40},{answer:'BRAVE',marks:30}
    ]
  },
  {
    id:3,
    question:'Which of these animals do you like best?',
    answers:[{answer:"SNAKE",marks:40},{answer:"BIRD",marks:30},{answer:"CAT",marks:20}
      ,{answer:'BUG',marks:10},{answer:'MONKEY',marks:0}
    ]
  },
  {
    id:4,
    question:'What would be the group of friends you have in Hogwarts?',
    answers:[{answer:"POPULAR",marks:40},{answer:"SMART",marks:20},{answer:"WHATEVER I DONT CARE",marks:10}
      ,{answer:'NO FRIENDS',marks:0},{answer:'ATHLETE',marks:30}
    ]
  },
  {
    id:5,
    question:'What colours do you prefer?',
    answers:[{answer:"PINK & PURPLE",marks:0},{answer:"RED & YELLOW",marks:30},{answer:"GREEN & GREY",marks:40}
      ,{answer:'YELLOW & BLACK',marks:10},{answer:'BLUE & BLACK',marks:20}
    ]
  }
  ,
  {
    id:6,
    question:'Which job do you most identify with?',
    answers:[{answer:"MEDICAL JOB",marks:10},{answer:"HISTORICAL JOB",marks:20},{answer:"FUN JOB",marks:30}
      ,{answer:'LUCARATIVE',marks:40},{answer:'JOB INVOLING TECH',marks:0}
    ]
    
  },
  {
    id:7,
    question:'What would you do if a thief broke into your house?',
    answers:[{answer:"HIDE",marks:20},{answer:"CALL THE COPS",marks:0},{answer:"DO WHAT HE SAYS",marks:10}
      ,{answer:'FIGHT HIM',marks:30},{answer:'ACT AS ANOTHER THEIF',marks:40}
    ]
    
  },
  {
    id:8,
    question:'If you are a Wizard and you see a wounded animal, what would you do?',
    answers:[{answer:"HEAL IT",marks:30},{answer:"RUN AWAY",marks:10},{answer:"CALL ANOTHER WIZARD",marks:20}
      ,{answer:'DONT KNOW WHAT TO DO',marks:0},{answer:'MAKE IT DISSAPEAR',marks:40}
    ]
    
  },
  {
    id:9,
    question:'Do you feel happy annoying children?',
    answers:[{answer:"YES",marks:30},{answer:"SOMETIMES",marks:0},{answer:"ALWAYS",marks:40}
      ,{answer:'NEVER DONE THIS',marks:10},{answer:'NO',marks:20}
    ]
    
  },
  {
    id:10,
    question:'What should your House be',
    answers:[{answer:"ANYTHING BUT HUFFLEPUFF",marks:20},{answer:"NO IDEA",marks:0},{answer:"ANY ONE OF THE 4",marks:10}
      ,{answer:'SLYTHERLIN',marks:40},{answer:'ANYTHING BUT SLYTHERIN',marks:30}
    ]
    
  }
  
  
]
export default questions;